<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Afar Atlas </string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>

    <string name="afar_text_1"></string>
    <string name="contact_info">+251-911-289475\n +251-966-105455\n +251-913-235881 \n\n\n  1and0consultancy@gmail.com \n Logia Town
        \n Semera-Logia City Administration\n\nAfar,Ethiopia</string>


    <string name="zone1_disc">Awusi rasu constituents total of eight wereda namely,
        Ade’are, Millei, Chifra, Dubti, Assayta, Afambo, Elide’are, and Kory. The zone shares 280.22Km long international boundary
        with Eritrea and Djibouti Republic. Furthermore, the zone shares 154.32Km long regional boundary with Amhara NRS.
        The northern part of this zone shares zonal boundary with Kilbeti Rasu and the southern part of this zone shares zonal
        boundary with Gabi Rasu and Hari Rasu. A total of 17 towns located in this zone. Including, Samara-logia city administration,
        which is the capital city of the region. The zone covers 34,871Km2 of area, which makes it the largest zone of the region.
        The zone has a total population of 410,790 of whom 224,656 are men and 186,134 women (CSA, 2007).</string>

    <string name="zone2_disc">Kilbati rasu constituents total of eight wereda namely, Abala, Erebti, Koneba, Megale, Dalol, Afdera, Bidu, and Berhale.
        This zone encompasses various tourist attraction places. Specially, for geo-tourism. Both the highest and the lowest elevation of the region are found in this zone.
        The zone shares 328Km long international boundary with Eritrea and Djibouti Republic. In addition, the zone shares 321Km long regional boundary with Tigray NRS.
        The administrative capital of this zone is Abala town. The zone covers 31,151Km2 of area, which makes it the largest zone of the region.
        The zone has a total population of 350,111of whom 195,404 are men and 154,707 women (CSA, 2007). </string>

    <string name="zone3_disc">Gabi rasu constituents total of six wereda namely, Gewane, Gelealo, Amibara, Dulecha, Argoba, and Awash Fentale weredas.
        The zone shares 471Km long regional boundary Oromiya and Sumali NRS. The northern part of this zone shares zonal boundary with Awusi Rasu.
        In addition, the western part of the zone shares zonal boundary with Fanti Rasu. The zone covers 16,381Km2 of area. Furthermore, based on areal coverage,
        this zone is 3rd largest zone in the region. Moreover, this zone is well known for large scale modern irrigation schemes owned by different organization.
        The zone has a total population of 198,751 of whom 108,995 are men and 89,756 women (CSA, 2007). </string>

    <string name="zone4_disc">Fanti rasu constituents total of five administrative weredas namely, Gulina, Ewa, Awura, Yalo, and Teru weredas.
        The zone shares 108.5Km long regional boundary with both Amhara and Tigray NRS. The northern part of this zone shares zonal boundary with Kilbeti Rasu.
        In addition, the eastern part of the zone shares zonal boundary with Awusi Rasu and the southern part of the zone share boundary with Hari rasu zonal
        administration boundary. The zone covers an area of 11,268Km2.
        The zone has a total population of 246,822 of whom 140,741 are men and 106,081 women (CSA, 2007).</string>

    <string name="zone5_disc">Hari rasu constituents total of five administrative weredas namely, Telalak, Dewe, Dalifage, Semiroby, and Hadele’ela weredas.
        The zone shares 224.66Km long regional boundary with both Amhara NRS. The northern part of this zone shares zonal boundary with Awusi Rasu.
        The zone covers an area of 5,976Km2. Based on areal coverage, this zone has the least spatial extent in the region.
        The zone has a total population of 183,799 of whom 105,321 are men and 78,478 women (CSA, 2007).</string>


</resources>
