<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Afar Atlas </string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>

    <string name="Zone1"><b> Awusi Rasu or Administrative Zone 1 </b>  is the biggest zone in Afar NRS with approximate areal coverage of 34,
        846KM2 and perimeter of 918KM. The zone is bordered on the south by Administrative Zone 3, on the southwest by Administrative Zone 5,
        on the west by Amhara NRS, on the northwest by Administrative Zone 4, on the north by Administrative Zone 2 and shared international
        boundary with Eritrea on the northeast and Djibouti on the east.The zone has a total population of 410,790 of whom 224,656 are men
        and 186,134 women (CSA, 2007).</string>
    <string name="Zone2"><b>Kilbet Rasu or Administrative Zone 2</b> is one of the five zones of the Afar NRS with approximate areal coverage of
        <i>27,455KM2</i> and perimeter of<i> 812KM</i>. The zone is bordered on the south by Administrative Zone 1, on the southwest by Administrative Zone 4,
        on the west by Tigray NRS and shared international boundary with Eritrea on the northeast. The zone is highly endowed with minerals.
        The zone has a total population of 350,111of whom 195,404 are men and 154,707 women (CSA, 2007). </string>
    <string name="Zone3"><b>Administrative Zone 3 or Gabi Rasu </b> is one among five zones in Afar NRS with approximate areal coverage of
        <i>16,175KM2</i> and perimeter of 723KM. The zone is bordered on the south by Oromiya NRS, on the southwest by Amhara NRS,
        on the west by the administrative Zone 5, on the north by Administrative Zone 1 and on the east by the Somali NRS.
        The zone has a total population of 198,751 of whom 108,995 are men and 89,756 women (CSA, 2007). </string>
    <string name="Zone4"><b>Fantena Rasu or Administrative Zone 4 </b>
        is located on the western part of Afar NRS with approximate areal coverage of
        10,888KM2 and perimeter of 444KM. The zone is bordered on the south and east Administrative Zone 1, on the southwest by Tigray NRS,
        on the north by the Administrative Zone 2. The administrative center of the zone is Kelewan. The zone has a total population of 246,822
        of whom 140,741 are men and 106,081 women (CSA, 2007). </string>
    <string name="Zone5"><b>Hari Rasu or Administrative Zone 5 </b> \n is one of the five zones of the Afar NRS with approximate areal coverage of
        5,442KM2 and perimeter of 495KM. The zone is bordered on the south and east by Administrative Zone 3, on the west by
        Amhara NRS and on the north by Administrative Zone 1. The zone has a total population of 183,799 of whom 105,321 are men
        and 78,478 women (CSA, 2007).</string>

</resources>
